好吧，我们在中间
okay so we're in the middle of
解释了比特币的设计，我已经开始想要
explaining Bitcoin design and I've
gotten to the point of ask of wanting
可以在全球范围内发布所有交易的记录，好的，
there to be a global published record of
all the transactions all right okay and
这是与证书要求非常相似的要求
this is this requirement is very similar
to the requirement for certificate
上周的透明度，解决方案让人想起
transparency from last week and the
solution is somewhat reminiscent
尽管比证书透明性解决方案更复杂，
although more sophisticated then
certificate transparency solution and a
我们想要一个公共日志的名称，通常也称为公共分类帐，好吧
name we want a public log this is often
also called a public ledger okay so how
我们是否要建立自己的公共分类帐，以便每个人都同意
are we going to build ourselves a public
ledger so that everybody agrees on all
已经发生的交易以及他们达成共识后的交易
the transactions that have already
happened and further when they agree on
交易的顺序，因为如果Y尝试将硬币发送给Z和
the order of the transactions because if
Y tries to send this coin to both Z and
Q同时您知道我们希望第一个获胜
Q at the same time you know we want the
first one to win and the second one to
不管耶林是谁想要的
be ignored
whatever Yellin which one want which
事务是第一位的，第二位是第二位的，应该忽略
transaction was came first and which
came second and should be ignored okay
那么如何制作分类帐，这是一个坏主意
so how to make a ledger so here's a bad
idea
好主意实际上最简单的主意就是挑选一个人
well a good idea actually have the most
simplest idea is to just pick somebody
每个人都信任并请某人为您维护分类帐的人
who everybody trusts and have that
somebody maintain the ledger for you
每次您要进行交易时，您都告诉受信任实体
every time you want to do transaction
you tell the trusted entity what the
交易是它只是积累日志，并愿意提供该副本
transaction is it just accumulates a log
and it's willing to give a copy of that
登录到任何人，以便任何人都可以检查它，看看是否已经花费了硬币，并且
log to anyone so anyone can inspect it
and see if coins already been spent and
这实际上是一个好主意，如果可以的话，您应该
that actually is a good idea and if you
could possibly do it you should for
比特币设计师拒绝这个显而易见的各种原因
various reasons the Bitcoin designers
rejected this very obvious
简单明了的想法，根本原因是在一个大型系统中
straightforward idea and the fundamental
reason is that in a big system in a
在全球体系中，不可能有任何一个人人都信任的实体
worldwide system there's unlikely to be
any single entity that everyone trusts
而且确实是值得信赖的，例如，没有腐败的员工
and that is indeed trustworthy and has
no corrupt employees for example and in
您所知道的全球体系意味着我们无法拥有您所知道的美国
a global system you know that means that
we can't have the United States you know
政府，我是值得信赖的实体，因为
government
I'm the trusted entity because there's
世界上许多政府不一定信任美联储
plenty of governments in the world to
don't necessarily trust the United
对于任何其他单个政府而言，州也是如此，因此对于
States similarly for any other
individual government so really for a
全球体系，没有，这很容易与拥有
global system there's no it's it's easy
to argue against the idea of having a
单一的中央受信任实体，所以我们也要离开
single central trusted entity so that
leaves us way as well we want to run the
系统构成了一个由互不信任的参与者组成的系统
system make a system that's built out of
mutually untrusting participants where
我们可以幸免于难，因为参与者知道，所以这是一个
we can survive malice by you know by
their participants okay so here's a
这是一种不好的可能性，让我们让任何人建立一个
here's a bad possibility let's just let
anybody let's build a system on which
任何人都可以加入，这样一来就会有成千上万的计算机可以通话
anybody can join so it's gonna have
thousands maybe if computers will call
他们同行，他们分散在整个互联网上
them peers they're scattered all over
the Internet
他们每个人都将为我们的新产品运行该软件
and each one of them is going to be
running the software to for our new
任何时候有人想要进行新交易（例如Y）的加密货币系统
cryptocurrency system anytime somebody
wants to have a new transaction like Y
想要将硬币发送给ZY洪水，他们的新交易发送他们的新
wants to send a coin to Z Y floods their
new transaction sends their new
交易给所有同行直接发送给他们或其他设计是
transaction to all the peers to send
them directly or another design which is
实际上，比特币使用的是Y向一对夫妇发送新交易
actually what Bitcoin uses is that Y
sends a new transaction to a couple the
对等方，然后对等方通过单个TCP链接提供给
peers and then the peers afford it sort
of over individual TCP links to the
整个系统的其余部分，因此在每笔交易中最终都被发送给所有人
entire rest of the system so in every
transaction ends up being sent to all
同伴和同伴他们想要做的是他们每个人都保持一个
the peers and the peers what they're
trying to do is each of them maintain a
所有交易日志的完整副本，而我们真正想要的是
complete copy of the log of all
transactions and what we really want is
对于所有对等方，所有诚实的对等方都将其事务日志用作
for all the peers used all the honest
peers for their transaction logs to be
相同，他们会同意存在哪些交易，并且同样重要
identical they'll agree on which
transactions exist and just as important
这些交易的顺序，那么我们如何安排所有这些同行
on the order of those transactions so
how can we arrange for all these peers
最终处理它们登录的标题事务
to end up processing the heading
transactions they're logs in the same
订单当然记得为什么可能将交易发送给了您知道的Z
order remember of course why may have
sent the transaction to Z you know to
这些同伴并同时将其交易发送给Q到其他一组
these peers and at the same time sent
its transaction to Q to some other set
的同行，我们要确保尽管同行最终以
of peers and we want to make sure that
despite that the peers end up with the
即使Y试图好好对待，我对相同的日志也一样，但实际上我不
same with identical logs even if Y is
trying to treat well I actually don't
知道如何设计这种可能性，您可以想象的是同行
know how to design this one possibility
that you can imagine is that the peers
会以某种方式彼此谈论每项新交易以及每项新交易
would somehow talk to each other about
each new transaction and for each new
日志中的插槽将对应填充该插槽的事务进行投票，然后
slot in the log would vote on what
transaction should fill that slot and
拥有您所知道的多数，因为他们可能会合理地不同意
have the majority you know since they
may disagree legitimately if they
收到了不同的交易，我们有一个多数规则，说我们
received different transactions we have
a majority rule that says well we're
所有的同龄人都会看所有的票和交易
gonna all the peers are gonna look at
all the votes and the transaction that
得票最多的是将在日志的下一个插槽中投票的投票，然后
gets the most votes is the one that will
go in the next slot in the log and then
他们将在下一张幻灯片上再次投票，
they'll vote again on the next slide and
你知道也许你可以使这个工作，你必须知道谁
you know maybe you could get this to
work you'd have to know who all the
其他同伴是为了知道您占多数，而不必知道如何
other peers are in order to know what a
majority is you don't have to know how
有很多同龄人，您真的想确保您永远不要数任何
many peers there are and you really want
to make sure that you never count any
会多次出现，但实际上在像比特币这样的完全开放的系统中
peer more than once but in a completely
open system like Bitcoin actually we
无法做任何一件我们不知道有多少参与者的事情
can't do either of those things we don't
know how many participants there are in
比特币以及数字随着人们的同行一直在变化
Bitcoin and furthermore the number
changes all the time as people peers
加入并离开系统，所以我们不知道有多少同伴，所以我们也不知道
join and leave the system so we don't
know how many peers are so we don't know
此外，大多数人将无法可靠地计算选票
what a majority would be furthermore we
don't have a way to reliably count votes
这样即使假定是可取的，每个参与者也只能获得一票
such that each participant only gets one
vote even assuming that was desirable
例如，所以我们不能使用IP地址来决定它的不同票数
for example so we can't use IP addresses
in order to decide it's distinct votes
我们不能说每个IP地址获得一票或最多一票，因为
we can't say well each IP address gets
one vote or at most one vote because it
事实证明，伪造IP地址或闯入IP地址非常容易
turns out to be extremely easy to either
forge I P addresses or by breaking into
人们的计算机可以累积成千上万的真实计算机
people's computers to accumulate tens of
thousands of real computers that you can
控制，您当然可以让他们全都对您的投票
control and you of course would you can
get them all to vote on your
您可以让他们所有人在系统中投票，以便攻击者可能
and you can get them all to vote in the
system so an attacker could probably
相对容易地以某种方式积累多数选票
accumulate a majority of votes
relatively easily in a sort of
这样简单的设计，如果攻击者可以获得大部分
straightforward design like this and if
an attacker can can get a majority of
投票，然后它可以使用多数票来说不同的话
the votes then it can use this majority
to sit to sort of say different things
冲突的事物，但每次都占大多数，所以Z是否要询问系统
conflicting things but with the majority
each time so if Z asks the system oh you
知道先进行两次交易中的哪一项，因为您知道
know with which which of the two
transactions came first cuz you know
记住那个问题，担心的是y要花双倍的钱
that remember the problem were worried
about is that y is gonna double spend
一些硬币，所以它将花费相同的硬币-Q希望您相信
some coin so it's gonna spend the same
coin - Q wants you to believe that and
它会将相同的Q的硬币发送给Z和1c以便相信
it's gonna send that same Q's coin to Z
and 1c to believe that so maybe when Q
询问下一个要记录攻击者控制的多数的下一个事务是什么
asks what's the next transaction to log
the majority controlled by the attacker
可以说哦，您知道明智地转移到Q是日志中的下一个，并且
can say oh you know wise transfer to Q
is the very next one in the log and that
在此交易之前出现，并且当Z询问攻击者多数会
comes before this transaction and when Z
asks maybe the attackers majority will
说好，您知道转账Z在前，而另一笔交易到Q
say well you know the transfer Z comes
first and this other transaction to Q
位居第二，这意味着攻击者可以将q + Z欺骗为X
comes second and that would mean the
attacker can trick q + Z into X into
接受同一笔硬币，这是双花，这是一场灾难，因此，如果没有
accepting the same coin that's a double
spend and that's a disaster so without
一些非常聪明的主意，很难建立一个开放的系统
some very clever idea it's very hard to
build an open system
你知道没有受控的会员很难建立一个开放的
you know without a controlled
memberships very hard to build an open
您拥有可靠的投票系统的系统，但实际上比特币不太可靠
system in which you have reliable voting
okay but in fact Bitcoin doesn't quite
使用投票，但尽管如此，它还是设法解决了如何获得投票的问题
use voting but it nevertheless manages
to solve this problem of how to get
尽管恶意，但在一个总账上达成协议，所以这是比特币
agreement on a single ledger
despite malice so this is the Bitcoin
区块链
blockchain
在这一点上，有很多差异链系统，所以实际上
and at this point there's a lot of diff
chain systems out there so actually I'm
甚至不确定该术语指的是什么区块链，但我只是在谈论
not even sure what blockchain as a term
refers to but I'm only talking about
比特币现在还可以，所以目标是我们希望在一次交易中达成协议
Bitcoin right now okay so the goal is we
want agreement on a single transaction
再次登录，因为我们要防止重复支出，这是我们要
log again because we want to prevent
double spending and this we're going to
建立比特币可以构建包含所有内容的区块链
be building Bitcoin builds this thing
called the blockchain that contains all
所有硬币上的交易，所以它是一个单一的单个区块链
the transactions on all the coins so
it's a single a single blockchain that
与先前的系统一样，再次描述系统中的所有交易
describes all the transactions in the
system again as with the previous system
将会有很多同行，所以我们仍然有这种覆盖网络
there's going to be many peers so we
still have this kind of overlay network
看来每个对等体都在构建日志的副本和完整的副本
appears each peer is kind of building a
copy of the log and a complete copy of
交易记录在自己的内存中，我们不知道他们有多少个同s
the transaction log in its own memory
and we don't know how many peers they
是或有多少人，但它们构成了其中一种
are or how many there are who they are
but they form a sort of in one of these
覆盖网络发现有TCP连接，并且任何时候对等方都能听到
overlay networks spotted with TCP
connections and anytime a peer hears
有关新交易的信息，例如当Y要向其提交付款交易时
about a new transaction like when Y
wants to submit a payment transaction to
Z或Q，它将发送给一个或多个同级，而同级将淹没
Z or Q it's gonna send it to one or more
peers and that peers gonna flood the
整个系统上的事务，日志的建立方式，
transaction over the whole system the
way the log is built up the way that
建立区块链是因为每个对等方都积累交易并
blockchain is built up is that each of
the peers accumulates transactions and
PAC将许多交易成千上万个块，然后是
PACs many transactions thousands into a
block and then it's entire new blocks of
通过淹没新块再次真正添加到分类账的交易
transactions that are really appended to
the ledger again by flooding new blocks
整个系统，因此至少在理论上每个同伴都可以看到每个新事物
over the whole system so that at least
in theory every peer sees every new
区块链，因此区块链模型区块链由区块构成
blocks so the blockchain model
blockchains consists of blocks what each
块看起来像是上一个块的哈希，有点像我的
block looks like is the hash of the
previous block it's a bit like my
先前的交易中断交易系统，因此我们拥有
previous transaction broken transaction
system so we have the hash of the
前一个区块，例如前一个区块的加密哈希，有一组
previous block like cryptographic hash
of the previous block there's a set of
交易，所以这些都是您的个人跨度，您知道为什么要付款
transactions so these are individual
spans from you know why is trying to pay
排队或碰巧发生几百
queue or whatever it happens to be a
couple hundred of whole thousand
个人交易，每笔交易实际上和我一样
individual transactions and each
transaction is actually much as I
在它具有该硬币的先前交易的哈希值之前进行了描述
described before it has the hash of the
previous transaction for that coin which
通常会在先前的区块中存在
is going to exist in a previous block
typically it has deprived a signature by
该硬币的先前所有者的私钥，它是的公钥
the private key of the previous owner of
that coin and it is the public key of
新的所有者，因此该交易可以从以下原因转移资金：
the new owner so this transaction would
have that transfers money from why the
队列将包含Hugh的公钥和带有明智私钥的签名
queue would contain Hugh's public key
and a signature by with wise private key
加上先前区块中先前交易的杂凑，以及这些
plus a hash of a previous transaction in
a previous block as well as these
交易中有一个随机数，稍后我将讨论
transactions there's a nonce
which I'll talk about in a moment it's
只是一个32位数字，然后是当前时间，大致是系统的方式
just a 32-bit number and then the
current time roughly the way the system
起作用的是，同行积累了新的交易，大约每10个
works is that the peers accumulate new
transactions and roughly every 10
分钟，其中一个产生一个新块，该块应该是后继块
minutes one of them produces a new block
that should be the successor block
包含所有已发送到系统中的所有交易
containing all the transactions that
have been sort of sent into the system
从上一个区块创建以来的十分钟内
in the ten minutes roughly since the
previous block was created and if you're
如果有人告诉您他们要付给您比特币，那么在您接受之前
if somebody tells you they're paying you
Bitcoin then before you accept that
他们确实做到了，您需要观察区块链的发展，而您
they've really done it you need to watch
the blockchain as it evolves and you
知道区块新区块无处不在，所以区块链是
know blocks new blocks are signs
everywhere so the blockchain is quite
公开，如果您认为有人声称已经付款，则需要观看
public if you think somebody claims to
have paid you you need to watch the
区块链，直到您看到一个包含交易的新区块
blockchain until you see a new block
that contains the transaction that
您期望声称自己寄钱给您的人以及您的
you're expecting from the person that
claimed to sent you money and with your
在他们看来有效的公钥，您知道正确签名了吧
public key at them that looks a valid
you know correctly signed okay so
每个人每个人都必须注意区块链向所有人付款
everybody everybody has to watch the
blockchain for payments to them all
正确，那么谁创建了每个块，这个创建新块的动作称为
right so who creates each block this
action of creating a new block is called
采矿和用于生产新区块的技术通常也称为
mining and the technique that's used to
produce a new block is often also called
从某种意义上说，工作量证明需要大量的CPU时间才能产生
proof of work in the sense that it
requires a lot of CPU time to produce a
新块，因此生产新块实质上证明了您
new block and so the production of a new
block essentially proves that you
控制真正的实时CPU，您不只是在虚假的情况下挖掘新块
control a real live CPU and you're not
just mining new blocks on a fake
电脑新块
computer the new block
为了在散列时有效的新块必须具有一定的数量
in order to be valid a new block when
you hash it has to have a certain number
当然，如果您只取块的哈希值开头的零
of zeros at the beginning of the hash of
the block now of course if you just take
一堆任意交易，然后对它进行加密哈希
a bunch of arbitrary transactions and
you do a cryptographic hash on it it's
几乎无论什么数据的散列都不会具有更多的散列
highly unlikely that the hash of some
just whatever data is gonna have more
加密散列开头的数字不能超过一，二或三个零
than one or two or three zeros at the
beginning of the cryptographic hash
但是，正在挖掘区块的计算机可以在此处放置它喜欢的任何值
however the computer that's mining the
block can put any value it likes here
为了打结，所以采矿计算机所做的就是尝试不同的方法
for the knots and so what the mining
computers do is that they try different
通过随机数的不同随机值选择一个随机数
by different random values for the nonce
just pick one with a random number
生成器，将其粘贴在他们试图挖掘的块的副本中，
generator that'll stick it in there copy
of the block they're trying to mine and
然后他们将在块上计算哈希
then they'll compute the hash on the
block
他们将检查哈希中有多少个零和多少个前导零
and they'll check how many zeros how
many leading zeros are in the hash with
这个特殊的结是否足以应付零，我不知道有多少
this particular knots if it's enough
leading zeros I don't know how many it
是，但是如果足够，您知道大约几十个
is but it's you know sort of on the
order of dozens if there's enough
前导零，这是一个有效的矿，一个有效的区块，以及任何同位
leading zeros and it's a valid mine a
valid block and the whatever peer it was
发现该现时导致块哈希具有很多前导零
that found this nonce that caused the
block hash to have lots of leading zeros
可以在网络上泛滥成灾，您知道所有事情都是平等的
can flood this block over the network
and you know all that's being equal
那将是新的下一个区块和链，但通常是
that'll be the new next block and the
chain but typically the the hash of the
与任何给定的随机数一起阻塞，您知道将没有足够的前导零，并且
block with any given nonce you know
won't have enough leading zeros and the
挖掘同伴将不得不尝试另一个随机数，另一个随机随机数继续做
mining the peer will have to try another
nonce another random nonce keep doing
直到得到一个足够散列的散列哈希
that until it gets uh a block that
hashes to a hash with enough leading
零，所以这会占用大量CPU时间，哦，你知道这是随机的
zeros and so this takes a lot of CPU
time it takes oh you know it's a random
处理，但系统已经过调整，且零的数量
process but the system is sort of tuned
and the number of zeros that are
设置必须存在于块的散列的开头，以便它
required to exist at the beginning of
the hash of the block is set so that it
与所有不同的同行大约需要十分钟的时间
takes about ten minutes you know with
all the different peers hundreds of
那里有成千上万的人在进行比特币的平均挖矿
thousands appears out there who are
doing Bitcoin mining the average amount
在他们中的第一个找到一个具有
of time before the first one of them
finds a nonce for a block that has
足够的喂零点设置为十分钟
enough feeding zeros is set up to be ten
minutes
好的，所以请问同or或新同how如何发现其他同to来
okay so question how do peers or new
peers discover other peers to
是的，这是一个很好的问题，所以这有点参考
communicate with yeah it's a great
question so this is sort of a reference
到这个比特币对等网络中，如果我是新对等，你知道我已经安装了一个
to the this network of Bitcoin peers if
I'm a new peer you know I've install a
新计算机，我在计算机上安装了比特币软件，我想要
new computer I get Bitcoin software
installed on my my computer and I want
加入比特币网络，我如何知道与谁交谈以及如何知道
to join the Bitcoin network how do I
know who to talk to and how do I know
好吧，答案很简单，那就是比特币软件具有
well so the straightforward answer to
that is that the Bitcoin software has
内置在一大堆当前对等方的IP地址上，因此您的
built into it on the IP addresses of a
whole bunch of current peers and so your
第一次将软件启动到二进制源时，无论
software when you first fire it up into
the binary the source whatever the
您知道的比特币软件拥有大量IP地址，并且您尝试
Bitcoin software you know has a whole
bunch of IP addresses and you try to
与现有的对等方建立TCP连接，如果一切顺利，您将
make TCP connections to those existing
peers and if all goes well you'll be
能够连接到他们，你会说我是新手，请给我一份
able to connect to them and you'll say
look I'm new please give me a copy of
现在存在的区块链，他们将向您发送当前的区块团队
the blockchain as it exists now and
they'll send you the current block team
现在大约有几百个千兆字节，这就是
which is about a couple hundred
gigabytes right now so that's if all
如果一切不顺利，一切都会顺利进行，那么您可能会遇到诸如
goes well if all doesn't go well then
you may run into problems like for
例如，如果您的软件副本已经被恶意修改，
example if your copy of the software has
been modified by somebody malicious to
列出了一个由攻击者或
have a list of IP addresses that are all
controlled by the attacker or the
攻击者控制着您的计算机网络，因此无论您尝试使用谁
attacker controls your computer network
so that regardless of who you try to
连接到您最终实际上是在与攻击者的机器对话
connect to you end up actually talking
to the attackers machines it may be that
攻击者正在运行，您知道他们自己的隔离网络，并且您知道
the attacker is running you know their
own isolated network and that you know
您认为您新安装的软件认为它已经建立了许多连接
you think your newly installed software
thinks it's made a bunch of connections
比特币知道，但是在这种情况下，它们都是攻击者节点
the Bitcoin knows but whoops they're all
attackers nodes in that case a
您将获得的区块链将受到攻击者的监控
blockchain you'll get will be watching
controlled by the attacker
而且您很可能会遇到麻烦，并且您知道其中有一种选择
and you may well you will be in trouble
and you know there's pick one of some
对此的辩护可能是他的主要能力
defenses against this may be the main
well he
加载了正确的比特币软件内置了正确的比特币软件
loaded correct Bitcoin software the
correct Bitcoin software has built-in
区块链中最近区块的哈希值，这意味着如果您
hashes of recent blocks in the
blockchain and that means that if you
至少在您运行适当的比特币软件中连接到一些攻击者
connect to some attackers in your
running proper Bitcoin software at least
巴赫金必须从盒子中的第一个但又有数千个方块开始
the Bakhtin has to start with the first
however many thousand blocks in the box
如果下载它，它必须是正确的绝对错误的软件，由修改
beam have to be correct if you download
it absolutely wrong software modified by
攻击者，那么比特币就无能为力，那么这就是
the attacker then there's just nothing
Bitcoin can do to help you then this is
我不一定听说过的系统潜在漏洞
a potential weakness in the system I
haven't necessarily heard of anybody
利用这一点，但这绝对是要考虑的事情
exploiting this but it's definitely
something to think about
好回到采矿好，所以如果你想创建一个新的块，你必须找到一个
ok back to mining ok so the if you want
to create a new block you gotta find a
导致您尝试生成新块的随机数导致哈希具有
nonce that causes the new block you're
trying to produce causes hash to have
对于单个机器，很多前导零都知道您需要花费多少时间
lots of leading zeros for an individual
machine you know the amount of time for
一台普通的计算机来查找满足此要求的随机数
an individual ordinary computer to find
a nonce that satisfies this requirement
至少要花一个月的CPU时间，但是有很多
is like at least in a months of CPU time
but there's a very large number of
比特币矿工在那里，所以即使他们中的任何一个都需要很
Bitcoin miners out there and so even
though any one of them would take a very
很长时间才能找到新的街区，或者我们真正关心的是
long time to find a new block or we
really care about is the time for the
他们中的第一个找到一个街区，因为他们都在做这种排序
very first one of them to find a block
and since they're all making these sort
随机数的随机数之一，其中一个会找到一个满足的随机数
of random choices of nonce one of them
is gonna find a a nonce that fulfills
需求相对较快，而比特币的数量会调整
the requirements relatively soon and the
number a Bitcoin adjusts the number of
响应新块的速度，在哈希中前导所需的前导零
leading required leading zeros in the
hash in response to how fast new blocks
似乎正在出现，所以如果新块出现的速度比
seemed to be appearing and so if new
blocks are appearing much faster than
每10分钟一次，比特币将自动增加
once every 10 minutes Bitcoin will
automatically increase the number of
所需的前导零，这将使其变得更加困难
leading zeros that's required and
that'll make it correspondingly harder
并花费更长的时间让矿工找到一个新的区块Nana区块当然是
and take longer for the miners to find a
a new block Nana blocks are of course
在持续的时间内到达速度比每10分钟慢
arriving slower than every 10 minutes
over a sustained period of time then
比特币将调整哈希中所需的前导零的数量为
Bitcoin will adjust the required number
of leading zeroes in the hash to be
更小，这意味着它会更快更容易
smaller and that means it'll be easier
quicker
找到适合您的一种自适应方案的模块
to find you blocks to the sort of an
adaptive scheme there to us blocks to
新的盒子每十分钟运行一次，大约可以了，所以这是
new boxes show up run once every ten
minutes roughly okay so this is the
工作量证明方案，这本质上是一种解决方案，并且全部
proof-of-work scheme and this is
essentially a solution and all in a
几分钟前我提到的那个投票问题的有趣方式
funny way to the that voting problem I
mentioned a few minutes ago where you
我真的无法进行某些练习，因为我们不确定
can't really have some practice I have
majority votes because we're not sure
参与者是谁或有多少人，因为人们可能会
who the participants are or how many
there are because people may sort of
创建伪造的计算机伪造的IP地址，无论您要在这里使用什么
create fake computers fake IP addresses
whatever it will here you have to use
CPU时间是一种无法按顺序伪造的真实资源
CPU time which is a sort of real
resource that cannot be faked in order
贡献一个新的块，这意味着你知道，虽然这不是一个真正的
to contribute a new block and that means
that um you know while it's not really a
表决方案，其本质上是从中获得新的障碍
voting scheme the what it's essentially
doing is the new block gets to come from
对涉及的不同计算机做出反应性随机选择
a reactively random choice over the
different computers that are involved in
在挖矿中，所以这种方案是一种随机的加密方式
in mining so this scheme is it's a sort
of a random sort of cryptographically
合理的随机选择过程，让谁可以选择下一个
reasonably strong random selection
process for who gets to choose the next
阻止，因此，如果攻击者数量很少，则极不可能
block and so if there's a small number
of attackers they're highly unlikely to
通过此过程选择，以便现在贡献下一个区块
be selected by this process in order to
contribute the next block now what that
意思是，如果大多数参与者或大多数CPU能力
means is that if most of the
participants or most of the CPU power in
该系统是由非恶意人员控制的，那么大多数新
the system is controlled by non
malicious people then most of the new
非恶意用户会发现这些阻止，这不是立即的
blocks will be found by non malicious
people and that's not an immediate
双重支出的解决方案，但我们会看到这是实现
solution to double spending but we'll
see that it that it's the key to the
双花防御好吗
double spending defense okay
好吧，让我们回到我们的例子，我们有一个区块链，也许
all right so let's go back to our
example we have a blockchain that maybe
看起来我们目前封锁了五点钟的罚款
looks like we currently block five
o'clock fine has been published to
每个人-他们所有的同龄人都在努力挖掘潜在的区块6
everybody the mmm them all the peers are
working on mining a potential block six
而且我们不知道会发生什么，因为矿工还在
and we don't know what's going to be yet
because because the miners are still
致力于寻找结，但您知道我们知道它有一堆
working on finding about knots but you
know we know that it has a bunch of
如果此时您为什么知道广播为什么说付款，那么交易很好
transactions in it well if at this point
why broadcasts you know say it's payment
到Z井，矿工已经在这个区块上工作了，所以明智的新方法
to Z well the the miner is already
working on this block so wise new
交易，即使它发出了，所以现在可能不会
transaction and even if it sends it out
so now probably not going to be
目前已经考虑合并到该区块中，但是所有矿工都将
incorporated in the block has been
currently mind but all the miners will
保留这种新事务并在一侧以及其中一个缓冲时
kind of keep this new transaction and a
buffer on the side and when one of them
确实找到了第6块的新块，然后将合并明智的交易
does find a new block for block 6 then
wise transaction will be incorporated
一旦有人想到了方框7，便开始尝试开采第7块
into the attempts to mine block seven as
soon as somebody does mind box seven
这个Y箭头Z实际上将在区块链中，所以一个
this Y arrow Z will actually be really
in the blockchain alright so so one
问题是可能会有两个不同的继任者走六个吗
question is could there be two different
successors to walk six could there be
诸如第7块和第7块的素数对，是什么阻止了这种结构
sort of a block seven and a block seven
prime right what prevents this structure
从产生，当然，我们对此感兴趣的原因是，如果
from arising and of course the reason
why we're interested in this is that if
然后结构就会出现
the structure could arise then
那么这两个也许是七个素数B七个双重素数，然后这两个不同的b7
then these two maybe seven prime B seven
double prime then these two different b7
s对b6的两个不同的连续继承者可能与Y的转移不同
s two different successive successors to
b6 might have different transfers from Y
因此，如果您只知道b7质数，就会想到为什么要支付它的比特币
and so if you were aware of just b7
prime you'd think why paid it's Bitcoin
看看您是否只是b7质数的素数，您将完全单击
to see if you were we're only a b7 prime
prime you this would click a totally
来自广泛急性的合法付款我的问题是可以有两个不同
legitimate payment from wide acute my
question is can there be two different
一个区块的后继者，答案是肯定的，实际上
successors to a block it turns out the
answer is yes and it's actually does
相当频繁地发生，原因是你知道
happen reasonably frequently and the
reason is that there's you know
数以千计的同行在那里挖矿，试图找到继任者来阻止
thousands of peers out there Mining away
trying to find the successors to block
六，他们可能正在开采，这是您知道要尝试生产的
six and they're likely mining it's you
know trying to produce somewhat
不同的区块，其中包含不同的交易集，因此很容易
different blocks with different sets of
transactions in them so it's easy to
想象一种情况，在这种情况下，您知道的一些同行碰巧看到了
imagine a situation in which some of the
peers you know they happen to see just
因为交易通过网络碰巧看到的方式
because of the way the transactions move
through the network they happen to see
为什么先将其转移到Z并合并以阻止其开采
why it's transferred to Z first and
incorporated in to block their mining
和其他您知道的同类产品，但它们的版本相同
and other peers you know for sort of the
same successors but the their version of
他们作为六位继承人的采矿区块恰好看到了这一点
the block their mining as a successor to
six just happen to have seen this
交易优先，并将其包含在区块中，以便我们轻松获得不同
transaction first and included that in
the block so we can easily get different
试图以产生不同继任者的方式工作的矿工是六个
miners trying to work in a way trying to
produce different successors to be six
如果其中两个碰巧发现一个随机数满足
if two of them happen to find a nonce
that satisfies the leading zeros in the
哈希规则同时意味着我们有两个不同的肿瘤块
hash rule at the same time that means we
have two different blocks to tumor
同时产生的完全有效的区块，它们都将发送
totally valid blocks produced at the
same time and they're both going to send
这些被封锁到网络中，他们会看到您知道
those blocks out into the network and
they'll be seeing that you know on
所有其他同龄人大约在同一时间，所以很容易这样
roughly the same time by all the other
peers so it could easily be the case
可能出现两个不同的两个截然不同的第六个继承者，并且
that two different two quite different
successors to block six may arise and
这叫做叉子
it's called the fork
因此，我们对Forks发生的事情非常感兴趣，因为这可以并且
and so we're very interested in what
happens to Forks because this can and
确实出现了最直接的规则，那就是任何同龄人看到
does arise well the most immediate rule
is that as soon as any peer sees a
接班人哦，您知道所有同龄人都在试图开采一个接班人来阻止六个
successor oh you know all the peers are
trying to mine a successor to block six
他们中的任何一个人比以往任何时候都更快地看到了新的继任者
as soon as than ever any of them any of
them sees a new successor block be
从成功挖矿的同伴那里涌来
flooded from some peer that did
successfully mine
它会停止处理六个，然后立即切换到尝试
it'll stop working on six and
immediately switch to trying to work on
b737的继任者，因此最初每个同行都看到其继任者
a successor from b737 so initially every
peer as soon as it sees a successor
块切换到为该后继块挖掘一个后继者，因此在此
block switches to mining a successor for
that successor block so in this
某些同行会首先看到b7 Prime，然后开始研究
situation some of the peers will see b7
Prime first and start working on a
继任者然后其他同行将开始我的工作，将看到b7 prime prime for
successor to that then other peers will
start mine will see b7 prime prime for
这只是取决于您知道他们首先会看到什么，如果这些
it's just depending on you know what
they happen to see first if the if these
两个人同时被开采，他们将开始为
two are mined at the same time and
they'll start working on a successor to
b7素数素数，所以现在我们得到了一些同行的努力，以扩展它
b7 prime prime so now we got some of the
peers working on sort of extending this
分叉在区块链中，其他同行正在努力扩展此分叉
fork in the blockchain and the other
peers working on extending this fork in
区块链，但是另一个关键规则是，如果有人
the blockchain however another critical
rule is that if a if somebody's mining
离开尝试制作这些区块之一的步骤，它会看到一个新区块
away on this trying to make one of these
blocks and it sees a new block for a
比任何人都在扩展这个叉子的更长的叉子
different fork that's longer then
anybody working on extending this fork
将切换为扩展此更长的分叉，因此这是软件中的规则
will switch to extending this longer
fork so that's a rule in the software
每个人都应该偏爱最长的链条，所以至少在最初，如果
that everybody is supposed to favor the
longest chain so at least initially if
我们有一些同龄人在一个叉子和另一个叉子上挖掘一种方式，
we have some of the peers mining a way
on one fork and the other and there's
相同的长度，而另一个在另一个叉子上挖掘，结果发现方差
the same length and others mining on the
other fork it turns out the variance in
产生有效的结需要多长时间
how long it takes to produce a valid
knots is pretty high
因此，即使有两个挖叉的同等数量的挖矿者，
so it's even if there's equal number of
peers mining both Forks it's highly
他们中的一个可能会比另一个更先找到继任者
likely that one of them will find a
successor significantly before the other
因此，此后继者将被淹没到
and so this successor will be flooded to
a bunch of nodes appears that were
在这个继任者上工作，他们都会切换到更长的Fork，所以
working on this successor and they'll
all switch to the longer Fork and so
这意味着这里存在某种不对称性，导致我们
that means that there's sort of an
asymmetry here that causes us a slight
你知道这个Fork itza是否在未成年人之前被未成年人延伸了
you know with if this Fork itza gets
extended by the minor slightly before
这把叉子，然后将矿工签到这把叉子上
this fork then that'll contract miners
over onto this fork it'll be more and
更多的矿工在这把叉子上开采，因此将发现更多的新区块，
more miners mining on this Fork and so
the new blocks will be found more and
胜利叉上的速度更快，因此有一种强化趋势
more rapidly on the winning fork so
there's a tendency sort of reinforced
成功的时间越长，一旦所有
success that's the longer fork gets
longer and pretty soon once all the
矿工们听说过这个更长的叉子，没有人会离开这个
miners have heard about this longer fork
nobody will be left the mining on this
分叉，每个人都会忽略它，每个人只会对待这个最长的时间
fork everybody will ignore it and
everybody will only treat this longest
像真正的链子一样叉，所以这很可能
fork as the real as the real chain okay
so this is it's highly likely that one
其中有一个叉子，两个叉子之一将首先看到一个x块
of the there's a fork that one of the
two Forks will see an x-block first will
每个人都更长的时间，所有的同龄人都将转向挖掘它，
be longer everybody all the peers will
switch to mining on it and that
每个人都会很快同意，其中一个当然是最长的叉子
everybody will rapidly agree that one of
the other is the longest fork of course
您通常知道大部分趋势中废弃的叉子上的交易
the transactions on the abandoned fork
you know usually most of the trend
通常，这两个竞争博客的内容非常相似
usually these two competing blogs have
you know pretty much pretty similar set
交易，但这里很可能会进行一些交易，
of transactions but there may well be
transact a few transactions here that
不在那里，当然，如果有人尝试这样做会花费或
were not there and certainly if
somebody's trying that will spend or but
如果废弃的叉中有未发生的交易
if there are transactions in the
abandoned fork that didn't happen also
成为赢家，那么这些交易他们就消失了
to be in the winning fork then these
transactions they just go away there's
没有尝试在区块链系统本身中尝试继承这些
no attempt in the sort of blockchain
system itself to try to carry over these
现在使用它进行交易，或者没有尝试直接合并
transactions now with it or there's no
attempt to kind of directly merge the
实际上，现在有两个分叉，您知道是否看不到您的交易出现
two forks now in fact you know if you
don't see your transaction show up you
也许发布它，你知道，因为区块链是
maybe issue it
and you know because the blockchain is
公开表明您的交易需要放心
public it'll become apparent that your
transaction needs to be reassured
因为它并没有更多地包含在获胜的叉子中，但是它也是
because it wasn't incorporated more in
the winning fork however it is also the
在很短的时间内，这些交易都在
case that for a brief period of time
both of these transactions were in the
区块链是正确的，因此在很短的时间内，
blockchain right so for a brief period
of time there was a double spending of
明智的硬币在区块链中，你知道这就像一个
wise coin in the blockchain and that you
know that's like a little bit of a
危险情况事实上，您知道这是一个极其危险的情况
dangerous situation in fact you know
it's an extremely dangerous situation
正确，因为整个要点是避免使用区块链，直到其中之一
right since the whole point was to avoid
block chains right until one of these
现在两个链变长了，现在还不清楚这两个链中的哪个
two chains got longer now it was totally
unclear which of these two chains to
相信，然后这些同龄人可能只知道其中一个或
believe and then these some of the peers
may only know about one of them or the
他们中的其他人，所以这引起了一个关于您Q或Z的问题
other of them so this raises a sort of
unhappy question about how Q or Z you
知道他们应该使用什么程序来确保已经实际付款
know what procedure should they use to
be sure that they've actually been paid
对，显然在交易完成后Z就说得还不够
right apparently it's not enough for Z
to say well as soon as the transaction
出现在区块链中，那么我确定我没有绘画，因为那不是真的
appears in the blockchain then I'm sure
I didn't paint because that's not true
对吧，也许这个酒吧连锁店最终会变得更短，
right maybe the maybe this bar chain
would end up being a shorter one and the
wipies Q区块链将同样赢得P你不能只看哦，你知道我的
wipies Q blockchain will win similarly P
you can't just look at oh you know my
交易显示在此区块和区块链中，因此它是有效的
transaction showed up in this block and
the blockchain therefore it's a valid
交易，因为它可能由于在较短的叉子上而最终被放弃
transaction because it may end up being
abandoned due to being on a shorter fork
因此，这就是该规则的原因，因为关心的人并没有真正
and so this is the reason for the rule
in that people who care don't really
相信交易，直到交易中有几个街区之后
believe in transactions until there's a
couple of blocks after them in the
区块链以及更长的链变得越来越长
blockchain and as a as the longer chain
gets longer and longer or as what you
认为链条越长，得到的机会就越长
think is the longer chain gets longer
and longer the chances that there might
是一些其他的链，它将变得更长
be some other chain that will become
longer in it longer than it could
消失得很小，因为如果您的链条稍长，
vanishingly small because if you're on a
slightly longer chain that's going to
吸引矿工在其上开采，因此没有其他链可以非常迅速地发展
attract miners to mining on it so no
other chain can grow very rapidly and of
当然，您知道特定叉子的链增长速度是
course the you know the rate in which a
chain a particular fork can grow is
与在该链上进行挖掘的对等点数量成正比
proportional to the number of peers that
are mining on that chain
好的，所以这是阻止它的机制
all right so this is this is the
mechanism that prevents with it makes it
因此，如果Y发出了两个同时发生的冲突交易，
so that if Y sends out two conflicting
transaction that's at the same time even
尽管如果有叉子的话，可能会有短暂的双花，但是很快就会
though there can be a brief double spend
if there's a fork it will rapidly be
两个交易中只有一个或另一个交易时间最长
only one or the other of the two
transactions will be in the longest
链，所以其中一个现在将以某种形式赢得官方链，您知道
chain and so one of them will win in the
sort of official chain now and you know
的确，如果第二笔交易出现，则稍后再发送给同级
indeed if if this second transaction
shows up is sent to peers later on after
Y链中的疾病传播，那么所有同龄人都将忽略新趋势
the Y transfer disease in the chain then
all the peers will ignore trend newly
对于已经花费在
arriving transactions that for coins
that have already been spent in a
他们正在挖掘的叉子上的链上交易，为什么你不能
transaction on the chain on the fork
that they're mining for so why can't you
知道在第一个交易出现后再次发送此交易
know send out this transaction again
after the first transactions shows up in
区块链中的链条好吧好吧，所以你知道还有其他一些攻击
the chain in the blockchain okay okay so
you know there's some other attacks you
可能会怀疑一个问题是，您是否知道让我们假设
might wonder about one question is
whether you know let's suppose that this
如果Y与某些同伴共谋，这是链条，这是
is the this is the chain if Y is
colluding with some peers and this is
官方的b7，我们有b8等
the official b7 and we have a b8 etc you
know
假设为什么不与某些同龄人出现联盟，请采取以下措施
supposing why isn't League with some of
the peers could appear take this block
七个现在您已经知道了在链的中间并将其更改为
seven it's now you know in the middle of
the chain and change it to produce just
一个没有交易的不同区块，只是
a different block that doesn't have this
transaction in it and just sort of
用这个新块代替旧块，然后假装那个
substitute this new block for the old
block seven and sort of pretend that
块e引用了它，现在阻止了这个新的块七没有
block e refers to it and now block this
new block seven doesn't have a
交易，这样一种非常简单的更改
transaction and so that sort of very
straightforward changing of a single
阻止不起作用，原因是这里的这些箭头确实非常
block doesn't work and the reason is
that these arrows here are really really
意味着有一个加密哈希，博客吃了
是它所引用的块7的哈希，所以您知道这个哈希封锁
is the hash of the block seven it refers
to and so this hashing blockade you know
对于已经存在的第七个区块，该哈希器第八个区块是
for for a block seven that already
exists this hashman block eight is a
如果有人更改此内容，则原始块七的哈希值将
具有不同的哈希值，因此如果您尝试典当，则此封锁哈希值
have a different hash and so this
blockade hash if you try to pawn off
这个修改过的区块对知道第八区块的人来说
this modified block on somebody who
knows about block eight they're gonna
说我们没有密钥，您知道哈希不会哈希到相同的no块
say we didn't have our keys you know
hash doesn't hash to the same no block
该块的七个素数不会散列到嵌入在Block中的相同值
this block seven prime doesn't hash to
the same value that's embedded in Block
E，所以您不能欺骗任何知道后续块的人接受
E so you can't trick anybody who knows
about subsequent blocks into accepting a
修改的中间块好问题
modified intermediate block alright
question
我知道为什么他的咖啡在Q店里出现在其中一个街区
I see why is a Q store by his coffee it
shows up in one of the blocks
哦，我知道了，所以这让我稍微备份一下，所以我认为
oh I see ok so this is a let me just
back up a little bit so I think the
我们遇到的情况是，您知道有一个区块链，然后是一个简短的分叉
scenario we have is that you know there
was a blockchain and then a brief fork
在那简短的分叉中，为什么要向两个不同的两个不同的硬币支付相同的硬币
and in that brief fork why pay the same
coin to two different two different
派对，我们说这是第7块素数，而第7块获胜
parties and let's say this is block 7
prime prime and it's block 7 that wins
并且在主链上，第7区块素数素数被遗忘，
and is on the main chain and block 7
prime prime is it's just forgotten and
忽略了，问题是jeez，您至少短暂地知道了Q看到了这个
ignored and the question is jeez you
know for briefly at least Q saw this
交易出现在链条中，然后为什么要喝咖啡
transaction show up in the chain and
gave the cup of coffee to why and then
为什么我离开商店，但随后您知道连锁店的这一部分被丢弃了，
why I left the store but then you know
this part of the chain is discarded and
Q没钱了，他们给了一些咖啡，但他们没有得到
Q is left with no money they've given
away some coffee but they did not get
如果Q愿意的话，这就是这种情况下发生的一切
paid and that just is what happens in
this scenario all right if Q was willing
在最后一次看到交易后，可以喝杯咖啡
to handle with a cup of coffee after
seeing the transaction in just the last
在区块链中进行封锁，那么他们会冒这种风险，他们一无所有
block in the blockchain then they'd risk
this scenario and there's nothing they
可以做到这一点，他们不能拿回我的钱，除非你没钱了
can do about it and they can't get the
money back I mean unless you run down
街上有人跟着走，拿走了杯咖啡，那就是
the street catch up with the person and
take the cup of coffee away and that is
您的星巴克手推车进行高价值交易的原因
the reason why for high-value
transactions your Starbucks trolley
不太在乎那杯咖啡真的只花了，就像你知道的50
doesn't care very much right that cup of
coffee really only cost like you know 50
美分，使他们喜欢，如果他们偶尔您知道这些叉子不会发生
cents to make like if they occasionally
you know these Forks don't happen that
通常他们偶尔会喝一杯咖啡，他们可能愿意
often they occasionally lose a cup of
coffee well they can probably willing to
处理这个问题，但是如果要从Q购买汽车的话，您知道20,000美元
deal with that but if if why was buying
a car from Q for you know $20,000
比特币谢谢你可能不想让Y走上这一水平
Bitcoin thank you probably would rather
not let Y walk off with this level of
确保得到付款，这就是为什么如果您在乎，您将等到
assurance that being paid and that's the
reason why if you care you'll wait until
交易所在的区块后会出现多个区块
multiple blocks show up after the block
in which in which your transaction was
因此，如果Z是一笔高价值的交易，他实际上不会将他交给他
in so Z won't actually him if it's a
high-value transactions he won't hand
直到至少有一些五六块出现
over the goods until there's at least
some number five six blocks showing up
在动作射击块打开后，它非常
after the block
Action Shooting open and it's very
一个叉子不可能像一个时期一样被延长五六次
unlikely that a a fork could be extended
at five or six times like over a period
现在，每隔十分钟就会出现一次ken block展示，然后显示为
of an hour now ken block's show up only
every ten minutes and then turn out to
是最短而不是最长的链，因为这意味着有一些
be the shortest not the longest chain
because that means that there was some
另一根延伸得更快的叉，这是之前其他方法唯一的可能
other fork that was extending faster and
the only way some other before could
扩展得更快的是，如果大多数cpu功能都在处理它，
extend faster is that if a majority of
the cpu power was working on it and
我们假设大多数的cpu权力是伊斯兰恶意的，并且
we're assuming that a majority the cpu
power is islam malicious and is
因此切换到当前最长的链就可以了，这就是你
therefore switching to the current
longest chain all right so this is you
如果您要进行大额交易，则必须小心，并且
have to be if you're doing large value
transactions you have to be careful and
等到链条走了很长时间，并且您的交易显示之后，好吧
wait till a chain goes long and after
your transaction shows up okay so okay
所以我解释了为什么您不能简单地在中间修改块
so I explained why you can't simply
modify a block in the middle of the
链中有一个相关的问题，那就是假设存在一个
chain there's a related question which
is supposing there's an existing
区块链，你知道那很长，而你的交易是Y arrow
blockchain you know that's something
that long and your transaction Y arrow
交易为什么他会出现在区块链中并且您想要摆脱
transaction why does he shows up here in
the blockchain and you want to get rid
您想现在以某种方式隐藏该交易，使其不存在
you want to hide that transaction now
somehow make it so it doesn't exist well
天哪，您为什么不生产一种新的替代链，您通常知道
gosh why don't you produce a new sort of
alternate chain that you know is mostly
与主链相同，但是更长，只是省略了Y
identical to the main the real chain but
it's longer and just happens to omit Y
被转移到Z，而是包括Y被转移到Q，如果您这样做
is transferred to Z and instead includes
Y is transferred to Q and if you do the
为此可以正确地进行挖掘，并且散列可以使您的链更长，而且
mining correctly for this and the hashes
work out your chains longer and it just
将被大家认为的比特币规则所接受
will be accepted under the rules of
Bitcoin which which everybody supposed
切换到最长的链条，那么为什么你不能这样做
to switch to the longest chain so how
come you can't do this
而且您知道这也将使您的支出翻倍
and this you know this would also allow
you to double spend by essentially
之前未用完的数量未用，而我之前对哦的评论是
unspent in a previous spent quantity and
my earlier comment about oh you're
应该等你知道zis等到区块链扩展
supposed to wait you know zis was to
wait until the blockchain gets extended
你知道这是现在击败Z等待区块链扩展的方法
you know this is now a way to defeat Z
waiting for the blockchain to extend it
所以我们真的是因为如果您可以使这项工作顺利的话，将会遇到严重的麻烦，
so we're really because serious trouble
if you could make this work okay so and
答案是肯定的，这可以使它起作用，这是如何做到的
somewhat well the answer is yes this can
be made to work and here's how to do it
您知道非恶意软件正在扩展主要区块链
you know the main blockchain is being
extended by the non malicious
参与者有一定的速度，他们拥有足够的CPU能力
participants at some rate right they
have enough CPU power to you know
如果您是攻击者，并且每隔10分钟就会产生一个新的区块
produce a new block every 10 minutes if
you're the attacker and you have more
比整个非恶意集出现的CPU功能，那么您将能够
CPU power than the entire non-malicious
set appears then you're going to be able
产生比真实链条更快的步行路程，因此您的障碍物使您知道
to generate walks faster than the real
chain so your block makes your you know
链可能会开始更短，我可能会花一些时间来生成每个区块
chain may start out shorter and I may
take you a while to generate each block
但您知道也许可以每十分钟生成两个块，而
but you know maybe you can generate two
blocks every ten minutes whereas the
主链每十分钟只能产生一个区块
main chain is only capable of generating
one block every ten minutes so that
表示您可能会赶上并超出
means that for a while you'll have
caught up and exceeded the length of the
主链主叉，根据比特币的规则，大家
main chain the main fork and by the
rules of Bitcoin everyone you
非恶意的完全正确的比特币同行，他们都将切换到您更长的时间
non-malicious totally correct Bitcoin
peers they'll all switch to your longer
连锁店，这意味着他们都会有效地忘记此交易，
chain and that means they'll all
effectively forget this transaction and
除了这笔其他交易之外，第二笔相同硬币的花费是
except this other transaction this
second spend of the same coin so if
您是攻击者，并且拥有的CPU能力要比整个其他产品高
you're an attacker and you have more CPU
power than the entire rest of the
网络，您可以生产此链，这意味着
network
you can produce this chain and it means
您可以花一倍的钱，并且您知道那肯定是您需要考虑的事情
you can double spend and you know that's
certainly you know something to think
关于但您可能希望更多的原因是有点自信
about but the reason why you might hope
more be sort of somewhat confident that
在一个有很多参与者的大型系统中，它不可能出现
it couldn't arise is that in a big
system with lots of participants it
可能很难组装比整个系统其余部分更多的CPU能力
might be very hard to assemble more CPU
power than the entire rest of the system
因此，一旦s头比特币变大，您就会知道人们有些自信
so once the buns Bitcoin grew big you
know people were somewhat confident that
非恶意系统的主要种类具有足够的CPU能力
the main sort of non-malicious system
had enough cpu power that it would be
对于攻击者而言，组装更多的CPU能力要比其余的花费更多
expensive for an attacker to assemble
more CPU power than the rest of the
当然还没有新的加密货币的系统
system of course for new
cryptocurrencies that don't yet have
非常大的采矿作业实际上很容易击落
very large mining operations going
they're actually easy to shoot down it's
对于像比特币这样的新加密货币来说很容易，对您来说攻击者很容易
easy for a new cryptocurrency like
Bitcoin it's easy for an attacker you
知道出于何种原因而通过获得更多的CPU功能将其淘汰
know for whatever reason to put it out
of business by getting more CPU power
但是对于像比特币这样的大型系统，现在说
but for a big system like Bitcoin it's
somewhat difficult now that said the
调查过的人试图找出谁来控制挖掘CPU的能力
people who've looked into tried to
figure out who controls mining CPU power
比特币怀疑最大的参与者占总数的一小部分
and Bitcoin suspect that the biggest
players have fractions of the total that
离50％并不远，如果您知道其中的两个或三个
are not that far from 50% and that
certainly if you know two or three of
最大的采矿业务合并部队，他们将拥有多数
the largest mining operations combined
forces that they would have a majority
比特币的采矿能力，并可能产生类似这样的替代叉子
of the mining power in Bitcoin and could
produce alternate Forks like this so
这是一个令人不安的发展，您知道是否有动力
that's a somewhat troubling development
you know whether there'd be motivated to
做不好的事情，特别是因为在比特币中所做的一切都是
do something bad especially since sort
of everything that's done in Bitcoin is
公众会真正注意到，哦，天哪
public that's what people would really
notice that oh gosh that was a long
链，然后我们切换到一个链条，该链条起步很远，男孩会
chain and then we switch to a chain that
started way far back boy would people
曾经注意到，那你会知道破坏对比特币的信心并可能
ever notice that and that would you know
destroy confidence in Bitcoin and may
破坏恶意方希望达到的目标
undermine anything that the malicious
parties were hoping to achieve
所以既然您知道这非常昂贵，那么您实际上知道
so since you know it is very expensive
actually you know the big players in
在比特币上挖矿，我花了很多钱来购买挖矿硬件，
mining in Bitcoin I spent a huge amount
of money to buy the mining hardware that
他们拥有，所以他们可能不想破坏人们对
they owned and so they probably wouldn't
want to undermine people's trust in
比特币，因为那会破坏他们庞大的收藏合作伙伴的价值
Bitcoin because that would destroy the
value of their vast collections partner
好的，这里有关机械的任何问题都可以，所以我
all right any questions about the
machinery here all right so I
我可以问一个问题的问题一个问题是，这十分钟之间
questions that I can ask an answer one
question is that the ten minutes between
块实际上是一个严重的烦恼，这意味着如果我想买东西
blocks is actually a serious annoyance
it means that if I want to buy something
交易最多需要10分钟才能显示在区块链中
it takes up to 10 minutes before the
transaction shows up in the blockchain
甚至在第一个街区，你
at all
even even in the first block and you
知道我必须等10分钟才能拿到咖啡或
know either I have to wait around for 10
minutes to get my cup of coffee or the
店主必须在跨性别之前给我我的咖啡
store owner has to give me my cup of
coffee before the trans before the
区块链中的所有交易因此必须信任我，为什么我们不能
transactions in the blockchain at all
thus having to trust me so why can't we
缩短10分钟，实际上您知道10分钟
make the 10 minutes much shorter and you
know actually the 10 minutes probably
可以变得更短的实际原因为什么它不短是因为
could be made shorter the practical
reasons why it isn't shorter is that it
实际上，新盒子需要一段时间才能在系统中泛洪
actually it takes a while for new box to
be flooded over the system right after a
矿工找到了下一个区块，必须向其发送数千个比特币
miner finds the next block it has to be
sent thousands of peers Bitcoin over
网络连接速度可能很慢，并且可能需要一段时间才能完成
possibly slow network connections and it
may take quite a while before that block
所有其他同龄人都知道，这意味着有一段时间
is known to all the other peers and that
means that there's some period of time
其他同龄人正在挖矿或浪费时间在挖矿中
in which other peers are mining on
blocks or wasting their time mining
我被那些尚未搁浅的方块所取代，并且
blocks that are I've been superseded by
a block that hasn't yet beached them and
基本上是您花费在采矿上的时间浪费，浪费了尝试采矿块的时间
basically the fraction of time you spend
mining wasting of trying mining blocks
被取代与开采每个区块所需的时间有关
that have been superseded is related to
how long it takes to mine each block
与淹没该区块所需的时间相比，如果您进行
compared to how long it takes to flood
the block and so if you make the inter
块间​​隔越来越短，然后开始变得足够小
block interval shorter and shorter then
it starts to it gets small enough that
它接近了淹没新区块所需的时间，
it approaches the amount of time it
takes the flood new blocks and that
这将导致大多数码头浪费大部分采矿工作，并且由于矿工
would cause most piers to waste most of
their mining effort and since the miners
实际上是通过挖矿赚钱的，因为有一点
are actually making money making Bitcoin
by mining because there's a little
奖励每个成功矿工的矿工们很无趣
reward to the successful miner of each
block the miners are very uninterested
浪费资源开采已被取代的区块等
in wasting resources mining for blocks
that are have been superseded and so
他们对这十分钟的兴趣不大，比这短得多
they're very uninterested in
this 10-minutes be much shorter than it
现在，您知道这是一个很大的限制，所以有一个
it's now and you know that's a
significant constraint so there's a
问题是什么阻止了为什么以后要花很多钱
question what prevents why from double
spending much in a much later block when
码头可能已经忘记了第一笔交易，所以您知道
piers might have forgotten about the
first transaction and so you know the
问题是，哦，您知道在很早的时候为什么根据Z转移并
question is oh you know in a very early
block why transferred according to Z and
然后有数千个区块，Y尝试将同一枚硬币转移给Q
then there are thousand blocks later Y
tries to transfer the same coin to Q you
知道像一年后或类似的东西，这如何进行的答案是
know like a year later or something and
the answer to how this plays out is that
所有的同龄人永远记住这一点，他们绝对记得每个未花费的
all the peers remember this forever
they absolutely remember every unspent
永远的交易，这意味着
transaction forever and that means that
实际上那不可能是我名义上第一个告诉你真相的人
actually that can't be the first
I think nominally to tell you the truth
我不了解这一切的来龙去脉，但最能理解的是
I don't understand all the ins and outs
of this but one way the most
解决这个问题的直接方法是让所有同龄人记住
straightforward way to solve this
problem is for all peers to remember
他们永远检查的每笔交易和每笔进来的交易
every transaction forever and every
incoming transaction they check to make
确保尚未花费硬币，他们只是在课程中创建数据库
sure that the coin hasn't been spent yet
they just the course create a database
或索引或其他内容，但允许他们本质上检查每条记录以查看是否
or index or something but allows them to
essentially check every record to see if
这个硬币已经用完了，我想你可以，尽管我还没有完全
this coin has already been spent and I
think you can although I don't fully
了解这一点，我认为同行可以抛弃很多，尽管很多
understand this I think peers can
discard a lot of though a lot of this
通过仅记住有关未花费交易的信息来获得信息
information by only remembering
information about unspent transactions
因此他们保留了未花费交易的数据库，但其中不包括
so they keep a database of unspent
transactions but it doesn't include
用过的硬币，如果新的交易硬币不在未使用的数据库中
spent coins and if a new transactions
coin isn't in the database of unspent
事务，那么它将被忽略，但是您知道该数据库必须是
transactions then it's just ignored but
this you know this database has to be
每对都必须永远保留此数据库，所以您当然知道
every pair has to keep this database
forever so you know just of course this
从某种意义上说，这是一个非常昂贵的系统，因为我们正在谈论的是您
is a in a way a very expensive system
because what we're talking about is you
知道基本上永远保持每笔交易的记录，而您
know maintaining a record of every
transaction essentially forever and you
知道您是否考虑每秒或每秒钟有多少笔交易
know if you think about how many
transactions there are per second or per
地球上有很多年，所以人们真的
year on earth
it's a vast number and so people really
认真使用比特币他们以各种方式使用比特币
were serious about using Bitcoin they
used it for everything in the way they
现在使用现金，您将知道这将是一个庞大的系统，并且会有
use cash now it would you know it would
be an enormous system and there would be
系统上的巨大性能流，实际上比特币并不是真的
enormous performance streams on the
system and indeed Bitcoin is not really
能够支持您无法运营整个财务的每笔交易
capable of supporting every transaction
you couldn't run the entire financial
当今存在的关于比特币的世界体系，有一堆
system of the world on Bitcoin as it
exists today and there's a bunch of
有很多限制，您知道一个限制是完整的比特币数据库
there's a bunch of limits you know one
limit is that the full Bitcoin database
已经消耗了几百千兆字节，是的，事实并非如此
already consumes a couple hundred
gigabytes yeah that's actually not so
不好，因为您可以将其安装在磁盘上，但是如果它大一千倍
bad because you can fit it on a disk but
if it was a thousand times larger it
甚至存储它也将成为一个严重的问题，更不用说搜索东西了
would start to be a serious problem to
even store it let alone search for stuff
这是最紧迫的问题，我们发现处理
in it the most immediate problem
and we it turns out that processing that
交易并不昂贵，因为对于同行来说，这主要是关于
transactions it's not terribly expensive
because for the peers it's mostly about
散列和这些加密哈希非常快，但大多数
hashing and these cryptographic hashes
are pretty quick but the sort of most
目前，您知道丑陋的限制是，这些块会限制
current you know ugly restriction is
that these block cuz there's a limit to
这些块有多大这些块只能有几兆字节的大小
how big these blocks can be these blocks
can only be a couple megabytes in size
而且每十分钟就会出现一次新方块，因此您只能
and new blocks appear only every ten
minutes and so that means you only get
您知道每笔交易每分钟不到1 MB的新交易
you know less than a megabyte of new
transactions per minute each transaction
您知道的Val的种类非常有多种缩写方法，但是
the sort of Val you know is very way
various ways of abbreviating them but
您知道每笔交易至少要几十个或一百个字节，这意味着
you know each transaction is at least
dozens or a hundred bytes and that means
该系统实际上只能由于该块大小限制和十个
that the system can really only because
of this block size limit and the ten
分钟限制，系统只能处理成千上万个
minute limit the system can only process
sort of thousands or tens of thousands
交易很好，我不确定我是否可以适当分配，但还差得远
of transactions well I'm not sure I can
divide properly but it's not nearly
足以运行当前的方式，即比特币的设置几乎不可行
enough to run the current way that
Bitcoin set up is not nearly
高容量足以运行世界上所有的金融交易
high-capacity enough to run the world
all the world's financial transactions
是的，所以您知道人们会改变它，但是它发展得还不够快
are and so you know people change it it
evolves but it's not really fast enough
当然，没有人真正将它用于商业用途
for everything of course nobody's really
using it for commerce it's mostly used
据任何人都可以猜测，所以这不是问题，而是
for speculation as far as anyone can
tell so it's not yet a problem but from
一个设计要点，需要修复一些东西，所以我提到了
a design point that there needs to be
some things fixed okay so I mentioned
在此之前，比特币软件会调整发现随机数的难度，即
before that the Bitcoin software adjusts
the hardness of finding nonces that is
块哈希中所需的前导零的数量会动态调整
the number of required leading zeros in
the block hash adjusts that dynamically
导致必须有十分钟的时间来阻止一件事
to cause there to be ten minutes for
block one thing that has to be the case
尽管所有参与者都必须就所需数量达成一致
though is that all the participants have
to agree on the required number of
前导零，他们实际上都必须就找到结的难度达成共识
leading zeros they actually all have to
agree on the hardness of finding a knots
因此，如果一种同等的方式看待生成区块的速率
and so if one peer sort of looks at the
rate at which blocks have been produced
除此之外，它太慢了，应该
and
besides that it's too slow and it should
使要求的前导零更少，但其他同行却没有做到相同
make the require fewer leading zeros but
the other peers haven't made the same
然后决定第一个码头将产生被拒绝的区块
decision then that first piers will be
generating blocks that are rejected by
其他同because，因为所有同the都要求他们认为正确的东西
the other peers because all the peers
demand what they think is the correct
哈希中前导零的数量，因此必须就
number of leading zeros in the hash so
there has to be agreement on on the
难以发现同行必须完全同意的观点
hardness of finding a nots
that the the peers have to agree exactly
以及当前的硬度是多少，否则它们会互相排斥
and what the current hardness is
otherwise they'll reject each other's
阻碍，所以他们如何达成协议，实际上是
blocks so how do they reach that
agreement it turns out actually to be
完全简单，他们毕竟都在看同一个区块链
totally straightforward they all are
looking at the same blockchain after all
重点是，您知道除了临时叉子以外，还有
that was the whole point is that you
know except for temporary Forks there's
只是每个人都没有一个完全相同的位的副本
just one blockchain everybody hasn't a
copy of the exact same bits in the
区块链，所以比特币只定义了确定性函数
blockchain and so the Bitcoin just
defines a deterministic function that
将当前区块链作为其参数，并使用它来
takes the current blockchain as its
argument and uses that to
确定性地产生当前的发现随机数的难度和方法
deterministically produce the current
hardness of finding a nonce and the way
它所做的基本上是看块中的时间戳来决定
it does that is basically it looks at
the timestamps in the blocks to decide
最近的区块产生的速度有多快，但自从每个人都在寻找
how fast the recent blocks have been
produced but since everybody's looking
在相同的块在相同的时间戳记中运行相同的功能
at the same blocks in the same time
stamps and is running the same function
调整硬度，他们都会得出完全相同的结论
to adjust the hardness they all come to
exactly the same conclusion about what
硬度应该适用于区块链中每个连续的块，因此
the hardness ought to be for for each
successive block in the blockchain so
那里正在执行一种有趣的协议，因为它们
there's a kind of interesting agreement
that's being enforced there because they
所有人都看到相同的法律
all see the identical same laws all
right
另一个有趣的问题是，某些人的动机之一
another interesting question is that one
of the motivations that some people have
对新的加密货币感兴趣的是
for being interested in new
cryptocurrencies is that they might be
比信用卡更具匿名性，而信用卡的确深深
more anonymous than credit cards and
indeed credit cards are deeply
匿名，因为信用卡公司确切知道您在做什么
non-anonymous since the credit card
company knows exactly what you're up to
我记录了它，而比特币至少在它的表面上，你知道
I keeps a record of it whereas Bitcoin
at least on the face of it you know
比特币没有关于说我名字的比特币交易的信息
Bitcoin there was nothing about a
Bitcoin transaction that say had my name
现在，您可能会想每个比特币都很好
on it
now you might think well each Bitcoin
交易中包含我的公钥，如果我不更改我的身份，那是真的
transaction has my public key in it
man that's true if I don't change my
公钥，我总是使用相同的公钥，然后有人
public key and I always use the same
public key then once somebody figures
拿出我的公钥相对容易，因为每当我付钱给他们时
out my public key is just relatively
easy since whenever I pay somebody they
他们知道我的公钥，然后人们可以通过
they get to know my public key then
people can track my activities by
在比特币锁中寻找我的公钥或签名，这是一个
looking for my public key or my
signature in the Bitcoin lock and it's a
公共日志，这样任何人现在都可以看到每个人都在乎的人，我认为
public log so anybody can look now
people everybody who cares and I think
大多数比特币钱包提供的价格实际上为每个生成新的公钥
most Bitcoin wallets offer actually
generates fresh public keys for each
我随时都可以说是交易，如果有人想付我钱，我的钱包会
transaction I'm said anytime if somebody
wants to pay me money my wallet will
生成在公钥对之前从未使用过的新密钥
generate a new never used before public
private key pair
记住私钥，然后将公钥提供给想要的人
remember the private key then give the
public key to the person who wants to
寄钱给我，这会使追踪更加困难，但事实证明，如果
send me money and that makes the
tracking harder but it turns out that if
你要面对坚定的侦探，知道是否有足够的线索
you're up against determined sleuth
there's you know there's enough clues if
您经常进行交易，因为交易通常与您的交易息息相关
you make transactions often enough since
the transactions are often tied to your
真实的身份，例如，如果您使用比特币从亚马逊购买了东西，也许
real identity like if you buy something
from Amazon with Bitcoin yeah maybe the
比特币交易尚不清楚是你，但可能需要运送
Bitcoin transaction it's not clear it's
you but it probably needs to be shipped
由FedEx向您发送至您的家庭住址，这仅是一点点识别
to you by FedEx to your home address and
that's a little piece of identifying
那里的信息，这将使某人知道是谁
information there and that will allow
somebody to figure out it was you who
花了那笔钱，他们就可以往回走，看看哪里
spent that money and they'll be able to
straight track backwards to see where
这些钱来自于另一个关于你是谁以及你在做什么的线索
that money came from to get another clue
about who you are and what you're up to
所以实际上对业余爱好者而言，比特币对于严重
so in fact against amateurs Bitcoin is
reasonably anonymous against serious
对手比特币证明不是特别匿名
adversaries a Bitcoin has turned out not
to be particularly anonymous okay
有点让人失望，
a little bit disappointing from a little
bit disappointing for people who are
对隐私或进行毒品交易或资助非法活动感兴趣
interested in privacy or doing drug
deals or financing illegal activity
好吧，总结一下这里的关键思想是
alright
sum up the sort of key idea here is the
区块链就像一个公共账本，每个人都同意并且拥有
blockchain like a public ledger that
everybody agrees on and that has every
交易以及所有这些都有很多问题，例如可伸缩性
transaction on it and all that has a lot
of problems like with scalability if you
可以使它工作这是一个好主意，另一种关键技术问题是
can make it work it's a great idea
another sort of key technical problem is
现在如何在没有任何集中的情况下做到这一点
how to do this without any
centralization now whether the
有价值的财产的集中化或分散化并不是真的
centralization or decentralization of
valuable property is kind of not really
一个技术问题，但是如果您重视它，那真的很酷而且令人惊叹
a technical question but if you value it
then it's just really cool and amazing
但是有可能在没有中央信任的情况下就单个日志达成协议，而我
but it's possible to have agreement on a
single log with no central trust and I'm
使用参与者，其中许多参与者是积极恶意的，并且是最终密钥
using participants many of whom are
actively malicious and the final key
想法是在也有问题的地方挖掘工作量证明的想法
idea is that is the idea of mining a
proof-of-work where it too has problems
但令人惊讶的是，存在一种允许的技术
but it's very surprising that a
technique existed at all that allowed
这种伪造的IP地址攻击无法欺骗的协议
agreement in a way that can't be fooled
by these sort of fake IP address attacks
不会遇到与投票一样的问题
that doesn't suffer the same problems
that voting suffers that was a very
我要说的就是令人惊讶和有趣的发展
surprising and interesting development
all right that's all I have to say the
实际上发出了继续这种思路和下一个思路的某种方式
actually sent kind of continuing some of
this line of thought and the next
部分是一种不同类型的分散系统的演讲
lecture which is a sort of different
kind of decentralized system partially
建立在比特币之上
built on top of Bitcoin